// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "With what data structure can a priority queue be implemented?",
    answer: "Heap",
    options: [
        "Array",
        "List",
        "Heap",
        "Tree",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which one of the below mentioned is linear data structure ?",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [
       "Queue",  
       "Stack",
       "Arrays",
       "All of the above",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Program with highest run-time complexity is-",
    answer: "Tower of Hanoi",
    options: [
      "Tower of Hanoi",
      "Fibonacci Series",
      "Prime Number Series",
      "None of the above",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What data structure is used when converting an infix notation to prefix notation?",
    answer: "Stack",
    options: [
      "Stack",
      "Queue",
      "B-Trees",
      "Linked-list",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: " Which data structure can be used to test a palindrome?",
    answer: "Stack",
    options: [
      "Tree",
      "Heap",
      "Stack",
      "Priority queue",
    ]
  },

    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What would be the asymptotic time complexity to find an element in the linked list?",
    answer: "O(n)",
    options: [
        "O(1)",
        "O(n)",
        "O(n2)",
        "O(n4)",
    ]
  },
  {
    
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which of the following is not the type of queue?",
    answer: "Single ended queue",
    options: [
      "Ordinary queue",
      "Single ended queue",
      "Circular queue",
      "Priority queue",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "The data structure required for Breadth First Traversal on a graph is?",
    answer: "Queue",
    options: [
        "Stack",
        "Array",
        "Queue",
        "Tree",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Q-9: What is the value of the postfix expression 6 3 2 4 + â€“ *?",
    answer: "-18",
    options: [
      "1",
      "40",
      "74",
      "-18",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "How do you initialize an array in C?",
    answer: "int arr[3] = {1,2,3};",
    options: [
     "int arr[3] = (1,2,3);",
     "int arr(3) = {1,2,3};",
     "int arr[3] = {1,2,3};",
     "int arr(3) = (1,2,3);"
    ]
  },
];
